gigwise.com 2017-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Gigwise

Photo: 

**This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is given by You to Us ("User Information") via the web site located at www.gigwise.com ("Site"). This Policy is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details.** "You" shall mean you, the user of the Site. "We/Us" means Gigwise. The "Site" shall have the meaning as defined above. "Users" means the users of the Site collectively and/or individually as the context allows. "User Information" means the personal details, which may be provided by You to Us via the Site as described above.

We process personal data only in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and associated legislation.  
**  
Data Collection**  
When using the Site You may encounter areas such as games, competitions, forums, shopping or video services where You may be asked to enter User Information. Such User Information will only be used for the purposes stated at the collection point and/or in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

By entering Your User Information, You accept that we may retain Your User Information and that it may be held by Us or any third party company which processes it on Our behalf.

We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of User's behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various areas of the Site and, in addition, to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of Users that have been exposed to or who have clicked on their advertising banners. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook. Our systems are not designed to associate personal information with your activities (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

**Disclosure**  
We shall be entitled to sell or otherwise make available Your User Information in order to send You information about Us and Our affiliates, associated companies and organisations, for the following purposes including, but not limited to:

promotional and/or marketing material about products, services and offers;  
market research or compliance;   
transfers to third parties as required; and  
any requirements imposed by operational law

We are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties who request Your User information and Users should check the applicable privacy policy of such third parties.

**Cookies**  
You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognise repeat site visits and as an example, re-call your name if this has been previously supplied. We may use this to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Site, target the advertising and assess general effectiveness of such advertising.

Cookies do not attach to Your system and damage Your files. If You do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows You to deny or accept the Cookie feature. Note, however, that 'personalised' services may be affected if the cookie option is disabled.

**Opt-Out**  
You may opt out of some tracking cookies that will be able to identify you on other networks by using the following links:  
<http://www.quantcast.com/docs/display/legal/Opt-out+of+Quantcast+Delivery>  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Security**  
Security is very important to Us. Security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of Your User information. Your User information will not be kept longer than is necessary for the purposes stated at the collection point or in this Privacy Policy.

**Updates**  
You may notify Us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected User Information by using the E-mail address below or the Contact section on the site.
